// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Who is founder of c++ language?",
  answer: "Bjarne Stroustrup",
  options: [
    "Mads Torgersen",
    "Dennis Ritchie",
    "Bjarne Stroustrup",
    "Anders Hejlsberg"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 2,
  question: "What is c++?",
  answer: " Programming language",
  options: [
    " Programming language",
    "Photo editing",
    "Language",
    "application"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 3,
  question: "C++ allows us to.",
  answer: " Allocate the memory",
  options: [
    "Application deveploment",
    "Cyber security",
    "Allow programing",
    " Allocate the memory"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 4,
  question: "c++ is a _ type of language.",
  answer: "Object-oriented programming language",
  options: [
    "User interface devlopment",
    "Application programing",
    "Object-oriented programming language",
    "IOS devlopment"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "C++ is a which level language?",
  answer: "High-level",
  options: [
    "High-level",
    "Low-level",
    "Median-lever",
    "Advance-level"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "C++ is also called as?",
  answer: "Scripting language",
  options: [
    "Scripting language",
    "Coding language",
    "Perfomance language",
    "Web degining language"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "C or C++ both are same ?",
  answer: "No",
  options: [
    "Yes",
    "No",
    "Little bite",
    "A or C"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "What is the extencion of C++?",
  answer: ".cpp",
  options: [
    ".c++",
    ".exe",
    ".cpp",
    ".cp"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "c++ is a ",
  answer: "Extencion",
  options: [
    "Extencion",
    "Code",
    "String",
    "Variable"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is the function of include iostream??",
  answer: "Insert data into a stream",
  options: [
    "Ranking",
    "Commenting code",
    "Insert data into a stream",
    "C++ extencion"
  ]
},
// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
// but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

//   {
//   numb: 6,
//   question: "Your Question is Here",
//   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
//   options: [
//     "Option 1",
//     "option 2",
//     "option 3",
//     "option 4"
//   ]
// },
];